[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Camp Rock character, played by Jasmine Richards, sings on her own at Final Jam surprising everyone with her voice.", "correct_answer": "Margaret", "incorrect_answers": ["Tess Tyler", "Mitchie", "Connie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name some ecologists use wen referring to Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "The eight continent", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "The island of Adam and Eve", "The garden of Eden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Cretaceous-Tertiary event, also known as KT boundary, refers to what?", "correct_answer": "a period of massive extinction of species", "incorrect_answers": ["The destruction of the largest pyramid in the Western hemisphere", "the first recorded devastating tsunami", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the homosexual painting brother of Claire and Gloria in the movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Todd", "incorrect_answers": ["Jaffe", "Jesse", "Zachariah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Vivienne Westwoods profession until 1971 when she started working as a designer?", "correct_answer": "Teacher", "incorrect_answers": ["Beautician", "Attorney", "Singer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of all mammals, giraffes require the least amount of which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Sleep", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamins", "Food", "Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Hebrew word gaon mean?", "correct_answer": "Genius", "incorrect_answers": ["Circumcisor", "The Old Testament", "Cantor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is Gocta Waterfall located?", "correct_answer": "Peru", "incorrect_answers": ["Venezuela", "Spain", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song was playing during the dancing montage in the movie The Breakfast Club?", "correct_answer": "We Are Not Alone - Karla DeVito", "incorrect_answers": ["Heart to Hot to Hold - Jesse Johnson  Stephanie Spruill", "Didnt I Tell You - Joyce Kennedy", "Fire in the Twilight - Wang Chung"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For a few seconds after exposure to strong light we continue to see the shape of the light source even after we dont look at it any more. What are these fleeting images in our brain called?", "correct_answer": "Afterimages", "incorrect_answers": ["Echoimages", "Preimages", "Printouts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The pink ribbon is associated with raising awareness for what disease?", "correct_answer": "Breast cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Skin cancer", "AIDS", "Autism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Representatives of three of these species produce venom of their own. Which is the odd species?", "correct_answer": "Mosquitos", "incorrect_answers": ["Lizards", "Scorpions", "Frogs"]}]